4 months ago I turned $100 into
$2,700 and to this day as crazy as this
my sound I get asked every single day on
how I did it and that was 4 months ago
so today is a day where I'm going to
give you the true story and explain to
you how I turned $100 into
$2700 in one week trading Forex and most
importantly I'm going to teach you how I
did it the story is cool but on how I
did it is so you guys can do the same
thing as well so let's begin so this all
started with the hundred to the million
doll challenge so if you guys haven't
seen the series where I turned $100 into
a million or at least I tried in 60 days
my first attempt on me doing this I
actually blew the account so my first
attempt to turning $100 into a million
obviously I have to scale up I actually
blew it on my first try account
officially blown it is what it is I'm
not going to lie I was super greedy I
was up almost $600 on this trp and this
is because I got too greedy at the
beginning I you know s and forget too
much and I didn't close my take profits
as soon as I should have because I was
trying to flip $100 into 10,000 in one
trade thinking that a trade was going to
give me that much profit without scaling
in and adding new positions and getting
new liquidity and it was a lesson right
blew the account no big deal then I
started my second account so when I
approach my second account which is the
one that I took $100 to
$2,700 there I realized that I had to
learn from the mistakes that I had in my
first account that I did so the first
lesson was do not set and forget too
much meaning if you have a take profit
with a 23x on the account simply close
your trade out there so then you can
take another trade risking the profits
that you made on that flip so if you
were to lose that trade at least you are
starting back at again at the original
balance and you don't have to deposit
again so this was one of my biggest
takeaways that I actually ended up using
during the whole entire challenge
because I would constantly just risk the
profit on the next trade instead of
actually risking the whole entire
account size which I'll explain a little
bit more in this later in the video and
then secondly which kind of ties into
set and forgetting too much it's greed
right so I got pretty greedy because I
just wanted to flip it super fast but I
had to realize that that wasn't possible
so then I minimized my goals that I I
was setting for myself for the week so
my goal was to pretty much double the
account every single week and if I did
that every single week by the end of
about 70 to 85 days I would pretty much
be at the million dollar as crazy as
that might sound because with compound
inous things would scale really really
fast so now knowing what I did wrong
which was setting and forgetting too
much and being too greedy I simply took
away from the account on what I did
right and actually what I did right was
take a high probability trade setup so
on the first account that I blew I
actually was up money so I think I was
up about $200 $300 I just didn't close
the trade so the trade reversed and then
it hit my stop- loss so I took the same
winning strategy that I have and I
applied it to the new account on the
first trade because again the most
important thing is taking that first
good trade so you can get out of the
hole and as soon as I took the first
good trade I simply just said and forget
and I cut my take profit short so I can
get the margin and take the next trade
if you want to know more about the solid
trades that I take I give them away for
free all you have to do is subscribe to
the channel I literally give away the
trades for free where you can make money
and turn $100 to 2700 just how I did all
you have to do is hit the Subscribe
button like who doesn't want to turn
$100 to 2700 all you have to do is just
subscribe subscribe so this first trade
that I would take on this new account is
what I like to call a textbook trade so
a textbook trade is literally what it
means a textbook trade you want to take
a trade that is from the textbook what
is something that's from the textbook
it's something that is classic it's
something that has been seen in the
market hundreds thousands of times where
the pattern is pretty much set to repeat
itself why would you not want to do
something that is not set to repeat
itself it doesn't make any sense and
these are the following rules for a
textbook trade and it's what I use for
my first trade where I turned $100 into
about 3400 in my first trade first
things first you want to make sure you
are following the trend the trend is
your friend if you're not following the
trend you have already started wrong my
friend and you're setting yourself up
for failure second thing after
identifying a very strong trend is you
want to be buying at a solid level of
support or selling at a solid level of
resistance third is you want to wait for
a confirmation that it is rejecting this
level of support or this level of
resistance right because you want to
make sure that the trend is bouncing off
of a support level or resistance level
and the way you do that is by having a
confirmation rejection Candlestick also
known as the famous entry signal so
there's many different types of Entry
signals if you want to know mine all you
have to do is hit the Subscribe button
because I teach it for free and the last
rule which is the most important by far
other than the trading signal is going
to be the actual session that you take
the trade if you're trading such a
little amount of money you want to make
sure that you're actually taking the
trade at a session where it's going to
have momentum meaning the moment you
take the trade it goes right into your
Direction you don't want to take a trade
outside of session so you're simply
fluctuating in draw down which is
unnecessary when you can simply wait for
the right session and apply this
textbook trade and it go into profit
immediately and those are the four key
foundations to a textbook trade this is
what I use for my beginner trade that I
took on the 100 to the 2700 and pretty
much every single trade after that I can
guarantee you that is simply going to
give you an edge over the market versus
not having anything for example just to
put it into simple perspective it's like
like surfing trading is like being a
surfer so when you go to the beach to
surf the first thing that you want to
make sure is that there is waves you
want to make sure that the ocean is
giving you waves so you can surf if
there's no waves you can't go surf it
makes no sense putting that into the
market you want to make sure the market
has a trend the market has no Trend you
simply can't trade anything so after you
have identified that there's waves at
the beach now you simply want to make
sure that your board is waxed so when
you get onto it you would have grip or
whatever I'm not a surfer I don't know
simple analogy right so so you want to
make sure that you have your board so
you can stand on when you get on the
wave and you don't fall off taking this
to the market is you want to make sure
you have this level of support or
resistance known as the area of Interest
so the market can support itself so it
can push up or push down when the price
gets to that point and then going back
to the surfing analogy it's going to be
your entry confirmation your rejection
Candlestick that's pretty much going to
be the entry as soon as the wave starts
curving that is your your entry point
where you get onto the wave right before
it takes off and taking this pretty much
to the market this is your entry
confirmation for you to enter the trade
right before the trade takes off and the
last one which is I think the most
important is I don't know if you're
trying to surf at night with the sharks
so I think you'd want to surf during the
day when there's sun and you know
there's not that many sharks so it's the
same thing in the market you want to
make sure that you're trading at a time
when there's more volume versus not very
simple analogy everything I've explained
so far is to Simply get out of that
original starting balance this is so you
can get out of that $100 point which
honestly it's the hardest point so you
want to make sure you have the textbook
trading rules and you want to make sure
that you are not greedy and you're not
set and forgetting too much and you want
to make sure that you obviously are
taking the trade at the right session
this is all cool right this is going to
get you from the 100 to about $3 $400
but now how do you actually take that
into the 2700 well that actually leads
me to to my next point which is going to
be scaling into the account so this is
actually very tricky and it can be very
risky but obviously sometimes things
with high risk have a high reward so
scaling into the trade is probably one
of the most tricky things because you
don't know when to do it or you don't
know if it's the right thing to do and
when is it the right thing to do so when
it comes to scaling into a trade you can
only scale into a trade that you're not
using your own money what does that mean
how am I risking something that I'm not
using my own money let me explain so the
way I scaled with I think it was
$450 where I took it to about
$1,200 on the 100 to the mill challenge
is I would risk out of that $400 I would
risk $200 on a trade and as soon as that
trade is $200 in profit not only am I
going to risk those $200 in profit but
that confirm confirms to me that my
trade is now going in that direction so
you never want to scale into a trade
that is in draw down because that means
the trade is not going in your favor so
why would you put more money into
something that is going against what you
originally thought if something is going
where you originally thought then you're
going to put more money on it to keep it
as a simple analogy let's say you're
betting on horse races and your horse
that you bet on is in first place and
they're going to let you bet more money
on that horse to win or you're going to
want to do that because if your horse is
in first place you're going to want to
keep betting more money because he's
pretty much going to be the winner but
let's say you have a race with the
horses and the horse that you bet on is
in last place and you're going to keep
betting on him to win you're destined to
lose your money that makes no sense so
you're going to only want to bet more
money if they're winning well the market
lets you do this if you're in profit in
the trade and the trade's going in your
favor you scale in and you add more
position positions confirming once your
trade is in profit so the way you do
this is for example with the horse races
let's say you have the horse race and
the horse is halfway through the race
and you bet $200 and you can close your
position halfway through the race at
$200 where you simply close the position
there and as soon as you close it you
get that money and you bet it again into
the market so if the horse for whatever
reason loses the race you're not break
even you don't lose the money but if you
win you win another $200 which is on
free money so this is exactly what the
market lets you do but instead of you
actually closing the trade since you're
using leverage and margin you're able to
actually use that margin from the
account that is floating in profit so
you can actually bet another $200 and
the way that this is possible is you
simply go to your platform where you
took the trade and you just take another
one and then I entered the same exact
trade with the same exact entry signal
during the next session and that ended
up giving us a nice push where we now we
have the account at
$2700 now keep in mind your entry is
going to be a little bit later than your
first one same thing how when you bet on
the race your bet is not going to be at
the beginning it's going to be halfway
through the race so your payout is not
going to be the same keep that in mind
but obviously in the markets you can let
that run a little bit longer you can
minimize your risk so on and so forth
the point is when it comes to scaling in
is that you want to only scale in when
you are already in profit you do not
ever want to scale in when you're in
draw down and this is what a lot of
beginner Traders make a mistake in
because they think that they can never
be wrong they think that if the trade
goes against them it's giving them a
better entry it's giving them a higher
entry budy that's that's not how this
works if your trade's going against you
you're wrong you should not be risking
more money on something that you're
wrong you only start risking more money
when something starts going in your
favor so to simplify the scaling in is
simply taking on more positions at a
lower risk to reward rate but it's a
actually higher reward overall with a
lot less risk because you're only taking
scaled in trades when the position is
already confirmed that it is going into
your direction it's pretty simple and
this actually leads me to my next point
which is going to be the takeprofit
right because I would strategically
scale into trades only to double the
account either two or 3x the account I
would never really ask for more than
that that because not only would that be
exceeding my weekly takeprofit but I
would realize that it's going to mess
with my psychology I'm telling you guys
right now there is no other feeling like
flipping an account you flip an account
and you feel like you're a Superman you
feel like you're Invincible you could do
anything in the world nobody can tell
you anything cuz you have a superpower
you can make a lot of money with no
money and you're pretty much 200 300
Xing something within the hour within
the day where hedge funds take 10 years
to do that so it's a very incredible
feeling but it is also a double-edged
sword that can be very very very tragic
to your strategy and to your account so
the way you remove that factor and that
side of the sword is by Simply Having
targets to hit and once you hit them you
are done for the weak this obviously
takes a very strong mindset and it takes
a lot of willpower to actually close a
position knowing that it has potential
to do more but you have to do that
because you have to stay true true to
yourself and true to your trading plan
so as I'm scaling into these trades and
as I'm risking more money on them I
would simply close out as soon as I
doubled or tripled the account as soon
as I doubled or triple the account I am
done for the week I do not care if
there's another amazing opportunity
because even though I might think it's
super amazing my mindset is not fully
there my ego is through the roof my
emotions are high like you get this high
off the market that there's just nothing
that can compare to it so the easiest
way to not let that influence you to
either risking more or breaking your
rules is by simply cutting yourself out
of the market as soon as you doubled or
tripled your account if you break that
rule you're going to see how that edge
of the sword will come back to you and
now that we bring up this 23x on the
account I want to make something
extremely clear this is not something
that is sustainable this is not
something that you can do and make a
living out of trading I only recommend
to flip accounts when you have had this
as your third or fourth account in your
actual trading meaning you're supposed
to have a personal account then a funded
account then potentially a higher risk
account than a flipping account this
flipping account should never ever be
number one on your list why because it
is not something that is sustainable it
is not something that you can live off
of it is not something that you can do
week after week month after month it can
go great for 2 3 weeks and then go
terrible for a month as it did for me
for me it was great for two months and
in one week I blew absolutely everything
so you don't want to have this gambling
mindset that you can think that you will
be a successful Trader consistently
having these highrisk positions because
it simply will not work the faster you
treat this as a fun account the faster
you will succeed the faster you don't
the faster you will fail you need to
treat this account as an account that
does not matter it is not a priority you
tap into it whenever you want it is
simply to have fun if you lose the money
who cares it's a fun account if you make
money who cares it's a fun account don't
be entitled to the losses or the wins on
this account this is going to be crucial
to your longevity and it will factor in
greatly into your personal account your
funded account and your low to medium
risk account if you treat this one as
the last one with no respect as you
should it should not affect your other
three accounts keep that in mind because
this is going to be your longevity in
the markets where you don't want your
psychology to go out the window over a
$100 account and this mindset is what I
teach my students every single week once
we get on a call every single Sunday
where I give them my top two and top
three pairs that I trade for the week my
my students were actually part of the
hundred to the million doll Challenge
and they actually saw every single trade
that I caught and they were catching
them as well these trades that I give to
my students every single week lets them
make anywhere from $1,000 to
$1,500 a week as a beginner set and
forget Trader and if it's your first
time hearing set and forget don't worry
about it I can understand if you don't
understand it so I left the video for
you guys in the link below where it
explains to you exactly what set and
forget means and how it lets Traders
make anywhere from a th000 to $11,500 a
week as a beginner Center forget
strategy and this is the exact same
strategy that I use to turn $100 into
$300,000 in under two months and I
didn't do it alone I delay away all of
my students inside of the Discord where
they get on a call with me every single
week so if you want to know more about
the setf strategy make sure you click
the link in the description below where
that video explains absolutely
everything what we're about and if you
do I'll see you inside